http://www.owens.edu/about_owens/privacy/

Home / About Owens / Privacy
About Owens HomeBoard of TrusteesEqual OpportunityFact SheetGovernment RelationsHistoryInstitutional ResearchMaps/DirectionsMarketing and CommunicationsMission and VisionNews RoomOffice of the PresidentPublic Records RequestsStrategic Plan
Privacy
Statement
Overview
Thank you for visiting the Owens Community College website
and reviewing our privacy statement. Owens Community College does not collect
personal information about visitors to our website unless you choose to provide
that information to us. Owens Community College does not sell, exchange or
release information gathered from your visit to our web site to parties outside
the College without your consent. Once we obtain your consent, we consider it
valid until revoked by you.
Information Collected and Stored Automatically
If you visit our website, we automatically gather and store
the following information about your visit so that we can track the use of our website
in order to make improvements. This information is stored and used in the
aggregate only, and is not used to contact you personally:
The IP address from which you access our website.
The name of the domain from which you access the
Internet (for example, Verizon, Roadrunner, Comcast, SBC / AT&T).
The type of browser and operating system used to
access our website.
The date and time you access our site.
The pages, files, documents and links that you
visit.
The Internet address of the website from which
you linked to this website.
Cookies
In addition to information collected automatically, we may
also collect cookies, which are small pieces of information sent to your
browser by a website that you visit. Cookies are used to track usage patterns,
traffic trends and customer behavior, as well as to record other information
from the website. When you register on the website, cookies also allow us to
save information so that you will not have to re-enter it the next time you
visit. Many content adjustments and customer service improvements are made
based on the data derived from cookies. Information that we collect from
cookies will not be used to create profiles of users and only will be used in
aggregate form.
You may set your browser to refuse cookies from any website
that you visit. If you so choose, you may still gain access to most of the
College's website, but you may not be able to take advantage of some of the
interactive elements offered.
If You Send us Personal Information
The Owens Community College website will only collect
personal information which you knowingly and voluntarily provide by, for
example, sending emails, completing membership forms, registering for classes,
events, or other programs, responding to surveys or ordering merchandise. If
you provide us with personal information, we will normally respond to your
inquiry, request or order. We may also contact you to provide information about
College activities, programs, membership and development opportunities and
special events that may interest you.
Owens Community College will only share information about
you to other parties when one or more of the following conditions apply:
We have your consent to share the information.
We need to share your information to provide the
service or product you requested.
We need to send your information to companies who
work on behalf of Owens Community College to provide a service or product to
you.
We need to respond to subpoenas, court orders,
or any other legal process.
We find it necessary to protect and defend the
legal rights and/or property of Owens Community College.
Student directory information may be released without the
student’s written consent. Directory information includes: name, address, email
address, I.D., photo, telephone number, date and place of birth, major field of
study, participation in Owens Community College activities and sports, weight
and height of members of athletic teams, dates of attendance at Owens Community
College, degrees, certificates and awards received, and the most recent
previous educational institution
attended. If you do not want your directory information released, you must
complete this form requesting it not be released and file the form with the
Records Office.
Linking
Within the website there are links to non-Owens websites.
When you link to third party websites, you leave our website and no longer will
be subject to our privacy policy. Owens Community College is not responsible
for the privacy practices nor the content of non-Owens websites, and such link
is not intended to be an endorsement of the non-Owens website or its content.
Comments
Owens Community College is a large organization with many
people sharing responsibility for the content of our website. If you have questions
about this Privacy Statement, please contact us via email at webinfo@owens.edu.
